KUNAL JAISWAL

Full Stack Web Developer
-MBRDI

PROFILE

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 5+ years of related experience.

EXPERIENCE

Mercedes Benz R&D India

2020-PRESENT

- Developed web application using ReactJS and .Net Core to store all product related information and display those as per the requirement.
- Deployed web application to Azure.
- Developed Web Api and exposed them to Power Bl.
- Developed responsive capability site for our internal team.
- Planned website development, converting mock-ups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.

Mindtree Ltd.

2015-2020

- Lead a team of 5 members to automate the Promotion module for Mindtree by creating responsive web applications using ReactJS, C#, Rest API and MS SQL It reduced manual work by 80%.
- Developed and designed the architecture for social intranet portal where user can publish blogs, create event for organization level or for the specific group they are part of.

CONTACT

- **8653497134**
- contact.kunal13@gmail.com
- kunaljaiswal.online

SKILLS

- JavaScript, jQuery, C#, SQL
- HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap
- ReactJS, jQuery, AngularJS
- Net Core, Web API
- SharePoint Online, Azure

EDUCATION

Bengal College of Engineering and Technology 2011-2015

B. Tech. in Computer Science and Engineering

Tender Heart Sr. Sec. School

2009-2010

Higher Secondary

- Portal was built on SharePoint Online using ReactJS,
 C#, Rest API and MS SQL.
- Automated Chairman's Award process using AngularJS and SharePoint 2013.
- Trained 2 juniors to be the part of our team.
- Designed technical upgrade paths, incorporating requested functionality and performance enhancements.
- Assigned tasks to IT personnel and junior module staff, delegating work orders based on individual employee proficiencies.

St. Francis School

2007-2008 Matriculation